Finding aid for the James Coover papers Mus. Arc. 88
Coover (James) papers
- Manuscripts, XII (Box 25, Box 26)
  - Loose materials
    - Opus I: Sy Oliver (music), Sid Garris (lyrics)
    - Prelude to a Kiss: Duke Ellington (music), Irving Gordon and Irving Mills (lyrics)
    - Robbin's Nest: Illinois Jacquet and Sir Charles Thompson (music)
    - S'posin': Paul Denniker (music), Andy Razaf (lyrics)
    - September Song: Kurt Weil (music), Maxwell Anderson (lyrics)
    - Shake Down the Stars: Jimmy Van Heusen (music), Eddie De Lange (lyrics)
    - Sing, Sing, Sing: Louis Prima (music and lyrics)
    - Snare Drum Solos, Sketches, 1965: James Coover (music)
    - Speak Low: Kurt Weil (music) ,Ogden Nash (lyrics)
    - Stumbling: Zez Confrey (music)
    - T.F.T.: Jack Strachey and Harry Link (music), Eric Maschwitz (lyrics)
    - The Best Man: Fred Wise and Roy Alfred, (music and lyrics)
    - The Night has a Thousand Eyes: Jerry Brainin (music), Buddy Bernier (lyrics)
    - This is the Moment: Robin Hollander (music), Leo Robin (lyrics)
    - Thoughtless: Carl G. Lampl (music), Buddy Kaye (lyrics)
    - Till Tom Special: Charlie Christian (music and lyrics)
    - Time on My Hands: Vincent Yumas (music), Harold Adamson (lyrics)
    - Where or When: Richard Rodgers (music), Lorenz Hart (lyrics)
    - Yesterdays: Jerome Kern (music), Otto Harbach (lyrics)
    - You'd Be Hard to Replace: Harry Warren (music), Ira Gershwin (lyrics)
  - Bound materials
    Restrictions
    Some items in this sub-series are restricted. Contact the Music Library archives for more information.
- Other related material, XIII (Box 24)
  - Abbruch
  - Description of the Music-Timekeeper, with illustrations, patented by E.R. Fayerman
  - John Parry's Manual of Musical Terms and Various Other Subjects Connected With Musical Art, by T. McLean
  - The Literature of Music Bibliography: An Account of the Writings on the History of Music Printing & Publishing, by D.W. Krummel
  - Methods of Music Publishing: A Frank Explanation for the Consideration of the Tyro in Composition, by George E. Dunn
  - The Pocket Standard Dictionary of Musical Terms, by Oscar Coon
  - Private Libraries of Musicians and Musicologists: A Bibliography of Catalogs, by Siegrun H. Folter
  - The World of Music: Library Gets Rare Copy of Dictionary it hankered After for Half Century, by Ross Parmenter
  - "Writson to the Rescue"
- JBC Interviews, XIV (Box 21)